<Computer id="sterlingComp"
          name="Noah Sterling Laptop"
          ip="78.221.59.2"
          security="4"
          allowsDefaultBootModule="false"
          icon="DLCLaptop"
          type="2">


<ports>22, 21, 80, 443</ports>
<portsForCrack val="4"/>
<proxy time="-1"/>
<firewall level="6" solution="PRAXIS"/>

<encryptedFile path="home" name="My_Final_Message.dec" extension=".txt" ip="192.168.1.1" header="My final message">Hi.
My name is Noah Sterling, though if you're reading this you probably already knew that.

The reason I've encrypted this message so heavily was to prove a point. The reason I've encrypted this message was so there would be only one group
who would be able to decipher it. The reason I've encrypted this message was so I could expose a hidden threat lurking in the shadows of this nation.

You are that threat.

In the past several months, I came to know of an organization acting without scrutiny, free to operate without liability, under the false banner of "safety" and "security."

Its name is Nova.

With their seemingly unlimited surveillance, Nova is able to bypass any security measure and take a peek into everyone's private lives, no matter their age, race, or creed.
And given how much the internet is expanding, their sphere of influence only grows bigger with every passing day.
Sure, they haven't done anything bad with our information yet, but who's to stop them from doing that in the future?

This is why I encrypted this message. This is why I organized my suicide. I created a mystery only Nova could solve. And so begins the endgame.
Already the seeds of doubt have been sown within your own organization. It's only a matter of time before the public finds out about this.

Mahler, if you're reading this, I am merely the catalyst. It's up to you now.

- Noah
</encryptedFile>

<eosDevice name="noah-ePhone" id="noahPhone" icon="ePhone2" empty="false">
<mail username="NoahSterling@cytix.com" pass="Pr4xis"/>
</eosDevice>

</Computer>