<Computer id="policeCaseFile"
          name="96th Precinct Case File System"
          ip="46.39.112.55"
          security="5"
          allowsDefaultBootModule="true"
          icon="DLCServer"
          type="4">

<account username="koliver1" password="V76Yg5!" type="ADMIN"/>
<ports>21, 22, 6881, 443</ports>
<portsForCrack val="4"/>

<DatabaseDaemon Permissions="public" DataType="TextRecord" Foldername="casefiles" Color="29,45,122" AdminEmailAccount="lwren@nypd.gov" AdminEmailHostID="policeMail" Name="NYPD Case File Database">
<TextRecord>
<Title>BO-8</Title>
<Data>CASE FILE BO-8
Date: July 24, 2018
Key Persons: Vic Bristol
             James Buchan

On July 23, 2018 at 2:21 PM, Vic Bristol and James Buchan, ex-spouses, found themselves in an altercation.
Earlier in the day, the couple had argued about child custody matters, which resulted in Buchan leaving the premises.
However, at 2:00 PM, Buchan had returned, reportedly to reclaim some personal belongings of his. Bristol had gone up to
her bedroom to fetch his items, however Buchan locked the door behind her, making her unable to leave the room.
After phoning 911, Officer Deitmore and myself were dispatched to the premises. Buchan was arrested on the grounds of false imprisonment.</Data>
</TextRecord>

<TextRecord>
<Title>MK-3</Title>
<Data>CASE FILE MK-3
Date: September 13, 2017
Key Persons: Alan Perez
             Julian Dorne
             
On September 12, 2017, at approximately 10:30 PM, two masked males entered a 7-Eleven convenience store and stole $233 from the register at gunpoint.
The store's security cameras recorded the incident. One man pointed a gun at the clerk at the time, Alan Perez and demanded he fill the bag with money.
The second took another man, Julian Dorne, hostage as it appeared he spotted the incident from outside the store. Before being forcibly taken into the store,
Dorne had called emergency services and a dispatch was sent promptly. By the time officers had arrived, the two masked men had already left the store.
No evidence was left at the scene, however the two witnesses of the event have described the men as average build, average height, roughly 5'8. One of them
was also wearing a pair of white Nikes.</Data>
</TextRecord>

<TextRecord>
<Title>ET-5</Title>
<Data>CASE FILE ET-5
Date: August 20, 2015
Key Persons: George Yularen
             David Leatrou
             Ingrid Miles
            
[REDACTED]</Data>
</TextRecord>

<TextRecord>
<Title>QL-1</Title>
<Data>CASE FILE QL-1
Date: March 2, 2019
Key Persons: Jason Mardred

On March 2, 2019 at 10:03 PM, James Mardred reported his car stolen. It was a red Pontiac with license plate number KOP221. No security footage of the
incident was found. This theft is believed to be the work of the as of yet unidentified Pontiac Bandit.</Data>
</TextRecord>

<TextRecord>
<Title>SL-9</Title>
<Data>CASE FILE SL-9
Date: February 19, 2015
Key Persons: Joe Darke
             Neil Marshall

On February 19, 2015, after a long interrogation of serial murderer Joe Darke, a power outage had struct the entire area near the precinct.
While emergency power was restored quickly, Darke managed to escape the interrogation room. Darke ended up finding himself in the office of Detectives Gant and Skye.
Prosecutor Neil Marshall pursued Darke and quickly apprehended him, but not before Darke pushed Marshall into a suit of armour and killed him. Darke was quickly
arrested again and sentenced to death for his crimes.</Data>
</TextRecord>
</DatabaseDaemon>

</Computer>