<Computer id="credits"
          name="Murder Room Credits"
          ip="192.168.1.1"
          security="1"
          allowsDefaultBootModule="true"
          icon="chip"
          type="4">

<ports>22</ports>
<portsForCrack val="1"/>

<file path="home" name="CreditsData.txt">
%--- Murder Room ---

^An extension by Kwiper

^Story by Kwiper



%Music

^Cinematrik
Revolve

^Matt Mclean
Outrun the Wolves

^Tonspender
Irritations
Slow Motion
Broken Boy

^OGRE
snidelyWhiplash

^Kwiper
Catalyst

^Turbo
surreal sippin'



^All backgrounds found on wallpaperflare.com
Connection
Crystal Peak
Link
Network
Polymorphous
Web Of Lies



%Special thanks

^Spiderbenb
Hosting and streaming the HackerJam. Thank you for motivating me
to get back into extension dev.

^Aqua
Preliminary testing and feedback. 

^COVID-19
Giving me time to work on this, even though I ended up crunching for time at the end.

^Matt Trobbiani
You should know why at this point.

^And you
For playing through this extension, and hopefully some of my other ones.
You guys are the reason I keep doing this.



This is a work of fiction. 
Names, characters, businesses, places, events, locales, and
incidents are either the products of the author's 
imagination or used in a fictitious manner.
Any resemblance to actual persons, living or dead, or 
actual events is purely coincidental.

</file>

<file path="home" name="Message_from_the_dev.txt">So here we are at the end, and so begins another one of my long-winded messages I put at the end of my extensions.
Murder Room was probably one of the most unique projects I've ever conceived. It's actually an extension idea I've had in mind for a couple of years now.
I knew from the start I wanted to twist Hacknet's mechanics in some way, and the Case File and Forensic Analyzer systems, as well as the extension's general premise, were
inspired by Osmotic Studios' Orwell. The extension's episodic/chapter-like structure was also inspired by Orwell, but the anthology narrative style of the different cases
were inspired by two other detective games I hold near and dear to my heart: Ace Attorney and Danganronpa. The detective genre as a whole is one of my favourite narrative
genres, and I was excited to expand upon it in Hacknet.

Once again, I would like to thank Spiderbenb for hosting the HackerJam that allowed me to finally bring this project to fruition. As I'm writing this before the jam submission deadline,
I have no way to know if I won or not, but this extension was fun to develop nonetheless. The competition was fierce, and seeing everyone create their own unique spins on Hacknet
has been amazing. I hope people continue to bring more to this game. I am considering expanding upon this extension after the jam, adding some more content, adding custom music
and overall adding more polish, so stay tuned for that!

Anyways, I hope you enjoyed playing through Murder Room, and if you haven't already maybe consider checking out some of my other extensions!
Any feedback you have or comments you would like to make are always appreciated.

Until next time,
- Kwiper</file>

<CreditsDaemon Title="Murder Room Credits" ButtonText="Complete" ConditionalActionSetToRunOnButtonPressPath="Actions/CreditsActions.xml"/>


</Computer>