<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="jmail"
          name="Nova Mail System"
          security="2"
          allowsDefaultBootModule="true"
          icon="chip"
          type="4">

<account username="#PLAYERNAME#" password="rosebud" type="MAIL"/>
<account username="agentM" password="gravedigger" type="MAIL"/>
<account username="NovaDirector" password="grandmaster" type="MAIL"/>

<ports>21, 22, 25, 80, 1433, 211</ports>

<portsForCrack val="6"/>
<trace time="100"/>
<proxy time="1"/>
<firewall level="-1"/>
<admin type="fast" resetPassword="true" isSuper="true"/>

<mailServer name="Nova Mail" color="200,200,200" generateJunk="true">
<email recipient="agentM" sender="L" subject="Case File IU-6">Hello, agent.
As usual, it's time for another case. You know the drill. Check your case file for the case details.

- L</email>
<email recipient="agentM" sender="Mahler" subject="Final steps">Maurice,
Sterling's case just got opened up again, which means it's time to set things in motion.
What I need you to do is to set a trail from the good director's pacemaker. Time is of the essence here.
It's time to expose Nova for their transgressions once and for all.

- Mahler</email>
<email recipient="agentM" sender="George Yularen" subject="Re: The truth">I have no idea what you're talking about.
Your empty threats mean nothing to me.</email>
<email recipient="agentM" sender="Mahler" subject="Re: Final steps">Excellent.
With his death, Nova should be scrambling to pin someone as a suspect. They have no reason
to suspect you, however they will be going after me.
Before I leave, you should know I've finally decrypted the ET-5 case. Finally the truth about these bastards will be revealed.

- Mahler</email>

<email recipient="NovaDirector" sender="Maurice Graves" subject="The truth">I know what you've done.
It's time to end this.</email>
<email recipient="NovaDirector" sender="Hilda Riegan" subject="Re: Substitute overseer">Understood, sir.
I will oversee Agent #PLAYERNAME# for the time being. However, I do wonder, am I really best suited for this task? Couldn't you ask one of the other overseers?
</email>
<email recipient="NovaDirector" sender="Luke Skylar" subject="Monthly Agent Report">Good day, sir,
Attached is the latest report on all currently active Nova agents. Please look through the report at your earliest convenience.

Sincerely, Luke Skylar
Head of Analytics, Nova</email>
<email recipient="NovaDirector" sender="EnTech International" subject="Contract Update 2020">Greetings, George
As you are aware, EnTech has recently pushed an update to its investigation suite. As you rely on this partnership, we have felt these
recent developments require an update to our original agreement. We believe this will benefit both of our organizations.

Yours sincerely,
David Leatrou</email>

</mailServer>


</Computer>